ILR School Foreign Visitor Information /3060
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Foreign Visitor Information
1954-1965
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/3060
11 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Material regarding visitors from Russia, Japan, India, Netherlands, France, and the Philippines. Also includes material on visiting firemen.
8436144
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 12, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, January 14, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
8436144
- Foreign Visitors, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Visitors to ILR 1940's 50's, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Russian Mihailov + Malkov, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Japanese Team, Nov. 1959 (Hodges (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Visiting Firemen 1956, 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Visiting Firemen 1957 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Visiting Firemen, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Visiting Foreign Teams, General, 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Philippine Study Group, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- NATO Program, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Indian Training Program, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Dutch Human Rel. Group. September, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- French Applied Soc. Res. Group 10/54, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 13)